[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "You're not running this marathon yourself are you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "running", "this", "marathon", "yourself", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "No, I'm not running the marathon.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "running", "the", "marathon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "Tell me why you're doing this?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "why", "you", "'re", "doing", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "Well, you know, I think for one thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "for", "one", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "What is it about the human spirit you think that reacts in such a remarkable way to terrible natural disasters?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "about", "the", "human", "spirit", "you", "think", "that", "reacts", "in", "such", "a", "remarkable", "way", "to", "terrible", "natural", "disasters", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Well I think, you know, I don't if I like using the word reduces but it brings us to our most commonality of spirit.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "think", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "if", "I", "like", "using", "the", "word", "reduces", "but", "it", "brings", "us", "to", "our", "most", "commonality", "of", "spirit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "You must be very proud of him?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "be", "very", "proud", "of", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "JJR", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "RB", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "I mean it make you -- it must be a big adventure for them to come and do this?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "it", "make", "you", "--", "it", "must", "be", "a", "big", "adventure", "for", "them", "to", "come", "and", "do", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Yes, I went up and watch them train and it was beyond -- you asked me earlier was I going to run in the marathon, all you had to do is be there and watch them train and let them do it.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "went", "up", "and", "watch", "them", "train", "and", "it", "was", "beyond", "--", "you", "asked", "me", "earlier", "was", "I", "going", "to", "run", "in", "the", "marathon", ",", "all", "you", "had", "to", "do", "is", "be", "there", "and", "watch", "them", "train", "and", "let", "them", "do", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Pamela Anderson"]}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "There is a rumor that Pamela Anderson might be running with them, is that true?", "question_tokens": ["There", "is", "a", "rumor", "that", "Pamela", "Anderson", "might", "be", "running", "with", "them", ",", "is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Pamela Anderson's a force of nature.", "answer_tokens": ["Pamela", "Anderson", "'s", "a", "force", "of", "nature", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Pamela Anderson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Port Prince"]}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "And what was your reactions with all that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "your", "reactions", "with", "all", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "I was in Port Prince and my first reaction was that I assumed that it had been something that would be called a terrorist attack.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "in", "Port", "Prince", "and", "my", "first", "reaction", "was", "that", "I", "assumed", "that", "it", "had", "been", "something", "that", "would", "be", "called", "a", "terrorist", "attack", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Is he a bit of both?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "a", "bit", "of", "both", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "In effect, I think that a legitimate whistleblower is one who is the curator of the information that they're distributing.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "effect", ",", "I", "think", "that", "a", "legitimate", "whistleblower", "is", "one", "who", "is", "the", "curator", "of", "the", "information", "that", "they", "'re", "distributing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Very nosy?", "question_tokens": ["Very", "nosy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "What would you have got to say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "have", "got", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "I don't it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Really, really ever been on film?", "question_tokens": ["Really", ",", "really", "ever", "been", "on", "film", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "I don't think so, not that I've ever seen.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", ",", "not", "that", "I", "'ve", "ever", "seen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "Have you ever actually worked with her?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "actually", "worked", "with", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "I haven't worked with her, no.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "worked", "with", "her", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "Would you like to?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "ENN: I know and I think she's lovely but I haven't.", "answer_tokens": ["ENN", ":", "I", "know", "and", "I", "think", "she", "'s", "lovely", "but", "I", "have", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "So what makes her so special?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "makes", "her", "so", "special", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "If I knew, I'd be doing it.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "knew", ",", "I", "'d", "be", "doing", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Seriously?", "question_tokens": ["Seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "That's not right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nicholson", "Marlin"]}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ":", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Who are the ones that actually feel slightly in awe?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "the", "ones", "that", "actually", "feel", "slightly", "in", "awe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Where has been all of this, you know, you know, from - Nicholson and De Niro and Marlin and yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Where", "has", "been", "all", "of", "this", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "know", ",", "from", "-", "Nicholson", "and", "De", "Niro", "and", "Marlin", "and", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "... people like Ted Cruz?", "question_tokens": ["...", "people", "like", "Ted", "Cruz", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "He is, he is my American brother.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", ",", "he", "is", "my", "American", "brother", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Did you not?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "I met him on several occasions with -- I didn't know him well.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "met", "him", "on", "several", "occasions", "with", "--", "I", "did", "n't", "know", "him", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "What do you say to young people who want to get in to the Hollywood business and may be even their parents who are going to put their kids into this cauldron?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "young", "people", "who", "want", "to", "get", "in", "to", "the", "Hollywood", "business", "and", "may", "be", "even", "their", "parents", "who", "are", "going", "to", "put", "their", "kids", "into", "this", "cauldron", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "MD", "VB", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "My opinion is that we notice them because they're in that business.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "opinion", "is", "that", "we", "notice", "them", "because", "they", "'re", "in", "that", "business", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "What would you think about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "think", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "That's -- he's exactly right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "--", "he", "'s", "exactly", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "What is your overview of that relationship?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "overview", "of", "that", "relationship", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "Well, he was the big brother I never had quite honestly.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "was", "the", "big", "brother", "I", "never", "had", "quite", "honestly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Was he helpful in that sense?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "helpful", "in", "that", "sense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "We discussed everything, you know what I mean, and it was literally like a big brother, little brother relationship where we've talked about everything, I would talk about the abuse that I endured in school which is also in the book, the abuse with my parents and also the difficulties of having to go to work everyday instead of being able to play.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "discussed", "everything", ",", "you", "know", "what", "I", "mean", ",", "and", "it", "was", "literally", "like", "a", "big", "brother", ",", "little", "brother", "relationship", "where", "we", "'ve", "talked", "about", "everything", ",", "I", "would", "talk", "about", "the", "abuse", "that", "I", "endured", "in", "school", "which", "is", "also", "in", "the", "book", ",", "the", "abuse", "with", "my", "parents", "and", "also", "the", "difficulties", "of", "having", "to", "go", "to", "work", "everyday", "instead", "of", "being", "able", "to", "play", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "I mean does part of you Corey feel, fortunate to still be alive?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "does", "part", "of", "you", "Corey", "feel", ",", "fortunate", "to", "still", "be", "alive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "NNP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Thank God.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "God", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Corey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "I do it brilliantly but I can't cook anything else so this is like a little God send that's arrived because it's packed full of simple recipes for idiots like me, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "it", "brilliantly", "but", "I", "ca", "n't", "cook", "anything", "else", "so", "this", "is", "like", "a", "little", "God", "send", "that", "'s", "arrived", "because", "it", "'s", "packed", "full", "of", "simple", "recipes", "for", "idiots", "like", "me", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "RB", "RB", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "I mean for someone who's hopeless like me, what is the simple way to be a good cook?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "for", "someone", "who", "'s", "hopeless", "like", "me", ",", "what", "is", "the", "simple", "way", "to", "be", "a", "good", "cook", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "I don't believe you're hopeless.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "believe", "you", "'re", "hopeless", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Does your other half cook for you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "your", "other", "half", "cook", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "No, he doesn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "does", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Never?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "EINFELD: But he's actually so obsessed with this book and the fact that you can take something and problem solve.", "answer_tokens": ["EINFELD", ":", "But", "he", "'s", "actually", "so", "obsessed", "with", "this", "book", "and", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "can", "take", "something", "and", "problem", "solve", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "So talk me through what we have here?", "question_tokens": ["So", "talk", "me", "through", "what", "we", "have", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "We have chicken wings, which I'm very, very excited about for you.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "chicken", "wings", ",", "which", "I", "'m", "very", ",", "very", "excited", "about", "for", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Do you like chicken wings?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "chicken", "wings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "I do like chicken wings.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "like", "chicken", "wings", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["First Chili"]}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 542, "question": "What do you mean not bad?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "mean", "not", "bad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "It's the First Chili and secondly...", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "the", "First", "Chili", "and", "secondly", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "You and I, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "and", "I", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "CC", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Do you crack jokes as you're cooking?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "crack", "jokes", "as", "you", "'re", "cooking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "I drink wine when I cook.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "drink", "wine", "when", "I", "cook", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry"]}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Who's funny, you or Jerry?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "funny", ",", "you", "or", "Jerry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "I think Jerry is funnier than me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "Jerry", "is", "funnier", "than", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Who makes you laugh more?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "makes", "you", "laugh", "more", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "That was good for you.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "good", "for", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "ORGAN: Who makes you laugh more?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Who", "makes", "you", "laugh", "more", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "I definitely make him laugh, which is really nice and you have that experience when we run into each other in Los Angeles and you made him laugh.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "definitely", "make", "him", "laugh", ",", "which", "is", "really", "nice", "and", "you", "have", "that", "experience", "when", "we", "run", "into", "each", "other", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "and", "you", "made", "him", "laugh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Anyone from history, from modern times?", "question_tokens": ["Anyone", "from", "history", ",", "from", "modern", "times", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eleanor Roosevelt", "Edie"]}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", ",", ":", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Who would your dream dinner party be?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "your", "dream", "dinner", "party", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I would love Eleanor Roosevelt, the Beatles, -- little Edie and big Edie.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "love", "Eleanor", "Roosevelt", ",", "the", "Beatles", ",", "--", "little", "Edie", "and", "big", "Edie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Who would that be?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "that", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "My husband.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "husband", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Obviously, really?", "question_tokens": ["Obviously", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "(Inaudible), of course.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "Inaudible", ")", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]